Finding Aid for Housing Division (University of Michigan) Records
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Central Topical Files 1920-1978
  - 1940-1993
    - Inter-Cooperative Council (ICC)
      - Articles 1966-1968 (Box 9)
      - Development Committee 1952-1965 (Box 9)
      - Historical Materials 1961-1989 (Box 9)
      - Housing Inspection Reports 1976-1979 (Box 9)
      - Membership Contracts 1973-1981 (Box 9)
      - North Campus Development 1956-1987 (Box 9)
    - Interfraternity Council (IFC) 1985-1986 (Box 9)
    - Mediation Services 1978-1986 (training session) (Box 9)
    - Off Campus Housing
      - General 1981-1988 (Box 9)
      - Abandoned Possessions 1980 (Box 9)
      - Associated Housing Program 1971 (Box 9)
      - Discrimination Complaint Procedure 1988 (Box 9)
      - Greek Housing Needs 1984-1986 (Box 9)
      - Housing Capacities 1965-1977 (Box 9)
      - Housing Code Study Group 1977-1978 (Box 9)
      - Housing Inspection Reports 1975-1977 (Box 9)
      - Housing Survey 1975 (Box 9)
      - Information Day 1987-1988 (Box 9)
      - Leases 1968-1974 (fraternities and sororities) (Box 9)
      - Non-members 1972-1989 (housing for) (Box 9)
      - Policies-History 1965-1971 (Box 9)
      - President's Commission On 1965 (minutes) (Box 9)
      - Registration Program
        - Landlord Registration Letter 1984-1988 (Box 9)
        - Registered Buildings 1989 (Box 9)
        - Rental Lease Agreements 1978-1987 (Box 9)
      - Small Group Registration Program 1974 (Box 9)
      - Vacancy/Housing Rates 1971-1988
    - Order of Omega 1985-1988 (Box 9)
    - Privacy Ordinance 1989 (proposed) (Box 9)
    - Reports
      - Housing at the University of Michigan-Report of a Survey of American Students, 1965 (Box 9)
      - Report on the Role Between Fraternities, as Student Organizations, and the University of Michigan, 1980 (Box 9)
    - Residence Halls
      - General 1971-1981 (Box 9)
      - Leases 1985-1986 (blank forms) (Box 9)
      - Rates 1940-1992 (Box 9)
      - Surveys 1983-1984 (Box 9)
    - Sororities
      - General 1973-1986 (Box 10)
      - House Director's Meetings 1963-1971 (Box 10)
      - Rush 1957-1978 (Box 10)
    - Substance Abuse Education Network (SAEN) 1986-1989 (minutes) (Box 10)
    - Summer Promotional Program circa 1970 (Box 10)
    - WQBN Escort Service 1986-1988 (Box 10)
  - 1933-1992
    The Central Topical Files 1933-1992 series (5.5 linear feet) is arranged in alphabetical order and documents the Housing Office in its broadest sense; the files span the years 1933-1992. The "Goals/purpose" file provides good insight into the core functions of the office. There is good documentation on the Rate Study Committee through annual reports and yearly files. Reports (1940-1979) have been grouped under the heading "Reports" to facilitate easier identification. Report topics include international students at the university, freshman women's hours, experimental living units, and residence halls. Documentation on residence halls includes educational philosophy, historical building data, and an analysis of the students living in the dormitories.
    - Academic Advisors 1969/70 (Box 12)
    - Academic Counseling, Committee on 1973-1974 (Box 12)
    - Additional Student Housing Task Force 1977 (Box 12)
    - Affirmative Action
      - General 1973-1978 (Box 12)
      - Women 1972 (Box 12)
    - AFSCME Strike 1977 (Box 12)
    - Afro-American Cultural Living Units 1971-1973 (Box 12)
    - Ann Arbor City 1970-1975 (re: ordinances) (Box 12)
    - Ann Arbor Housing Commission 1970 (Box 12)
    - Area Concept Study 1969-1976 (Box 12)
    - Area Managers (includes monthly reports)
      - Central Area 1970-1971 (Box 12)
      - Hill Area 1972-1974 (Box 12)
      - North Campus 1966-1975 (Box 12)
    - Assignment Policies, Committee on 1969-1976 (Box 12)
    - Audit Reports, 1970-1976 (Box 12)
      (student residences with income pledged)
    - Big Ten Residence Halls
      - Facility and Operation Statistics 1969 (1953-1969) (Box 12)
      - Statistical Survey 1959-1976, 2 folders (Box 12)
    - Black Student Aid 1969-1970 (Box 12)
    - Breakfast 1971-1980 (Box 12)
    - Budget Information 1933-1976 (Box 12)
    - Building Directors
      - Meetings 1967-1972 (Box 12)
      - Seminars
        - 1968 (Box 12)
        - 1969 (Box 12)
    - Campus-Wide Area Recreation Facilities, Subcommittee on 1968/69 (Box 12)
    - Central Campus Housing 1975/76 (goals) (Box 12)
    - Centrum Proposal, 1973 (Box 12)
      (cooperative day care project)
    - City-University Coordinating Committee 1974-1983 (Box 12)
    - Coed Bathrooms 1974-1977 (Box 12)
    - Co-educational Study Committee 1969/70 (minutes) (Box 12)
    - Committee on 1969/70 Planning, 1968/69 (Box 12)
    - Conduct 1967-1976 (re: residence halls) (Box 12)
    - Cost Reduction, Committee on 1975 (Box 12)
    - Crime in Residence Halls 1967-1969 (Box 13)
    - Disabled Students 1966-1981 (Box 13)
    - Drugs 1969-1974 (Box 13)
    - Drugs and Narcotics 1968-1978 (Box 13)
    - East Quadrangle 1968 (Box 13)
    - Educational Integration of Residential Living, Proposal for 1968 (Box 13)
    - Educational Programming 1969-1975 (Box 13)
    - Energy Task Force 1978 (Box 13)
    - Fall Kick Off Address 1978-1992, 2 folders (Box 13)
    - Feldkamp, John (Director of Housing) 1966-1977 (speeches) (Box 13)
    - Food Service
      - General 1975-1978 (Box 13)
      - Consolidation 1978 (Box 13)
      - Small Group Housing 1970-1988 (Box 13)
    - Fraternities 1968-1981 (scattered dates) (Box 13)
    - Freshman Program Committee 1968-1969 (Box 13)
    - Goals/Purpose 1973-1981, 2 folders (Box 13)
    - Grievance Procedures 1977 (student) (Box 13)
    - Honors Housing 1972-1975 (Box 13)
    - Housing Division 1974 (re: name change) (Box 13)
    - Housing Statistics 1960-1982 (Box 13)
    - Housing Unit Committee 1974-1975 (conference notes) (Box 13)
    - Inteflex Program 1972-1974 (Box 13)
    - Inter-Cooperative Council 1956-1966 (Box 13)
    - Interfaith Center 1966-1969 (north campus) (Box 13)
    - Inter House Assembly 1966-1971 (Box 13)
    - International Center 1958-1961 (Box 13)
    - International Houses 1968-1972 (Box 13)
    - Kosher Co-op 1974-1975 (proposal) (Box 14)
    - Libraries, Residential 1967-1972 (Box 14)
    - Library Committee 1969-1971 (Box 14)
    - Live-in Requirements for Dormitories 1968 (Box 14)
    - Management by Objectives
      - 1974 (Box 14)
      - 1975 (Box 14)
      - 1976 (Box 14)
      - 1977 (Box 14)
      - 1978 (Box 14)
    - Married Student Housing 1965-1966 (Box 14)
    - Meal Policies 1967-1981 (Box 14)
    - Mediation Services 1972-1978 (Box 14)
    - Minority Occupancy 1972-1982 (Box 14)
    - Minority Peer Advisor Evaluation 1981/82 (Box 14)
    - Monthly Reports
      - Central Campus Area 1970 (Box 14)
      - Hill Area 1969-1974 (Box 14)
      - Family Housing 1971-1978 (Box 14)
      - North Campus Area 1971-1974 (Box 14)
      - Parking-Family Housing 1978 (Box 14)
    - North Campus
      - Planning 1973-1975 (Box 14)
      - Service Facilities 1967 (Hobbs Development) (Box 14)
    - Northwood V 1970-1978 (Box 14)
    - Northwood V Task Force 1976/77 (Box 14)
    - Northwood Recreation Development 1969 (Box 14)
    - Northwood/Terrace Association 1969 (Box 14)
    - Occasional Papers 1978 (Box 14)
    - Off Campus Housing 1968-1972 (Box 14)
    - Operational Staff Meeting Minutes 1971-1972 (Box 14)
    - Organizational Charts 1969-1982 (Box 14)
    - Orientation 1972-1976 (Box 14)
    - Parent Orientation 1974-1979 (Box 14)
    - Parking 1978 (family housing) (Box 14)
    - Planning Committee 1973-1974 (Box 14)
    - Program Evaluation Committee (PEC)
      - Questionnaire 1978 (Box 14)
      - Phase II 1979 (Box 14)
    - Project Awareness 1972-1974 (Box 15)
    - Psychiatric Emergency Committee Report 1979-1985 (Box 15)
    - Quadrangle Director's Meetings 1963-1966 (Box 15)
    - Rate Study Committee
      - Annual Reports 1975-1982 (Box 15)
      - Family Housing 1972/73 (Box 15)
    - Rate Study Committee (cont.)
      - Residence Halls
        - 1968/69 (Box 15)
        - 1969/70 (Box 15)
        - 1970/71 (Box 15)
        - 1971/72 (Box 15)
        - 1972/73 (Box 15)
        - 1973/74 (Box 15)
        - 1976-1979 (Box 15)
    - Regents' Retreat 1976 (Box 15)
    - Reports
      - The 1960 Survey of International Students at the University of Michigan1961 (Box 15)
      - Attitude and Opinion Study: Freshman Women's Hours and Visitation Policies 1968 (Box 15)
      - Attitude and Opinion Study: Freshman Women's Hours and Visitation Policies 1969 (Box 15)
      - Campus-Wide Food Service Study, March / April 1969 (Box 15)
      - Co-Educational Housing Study Committee Report 1970 (Box 15)
      - Fraternity Housing at University of Michigan 1967 (Box 15)
      - FY 1977/78 Energy Report University of Michigan Housing Division, 1978 (Box 15)
      - Housing at the University of Michigan: Report of a Survey of Foreign Students 1965 (Box 15)
      - Report of the Committee to Identify Additional Male Spaces 1967 (Box 15)
      - Report of the Committee to Study the Effective Utilization of Resources in Housing 1974 (Box 15)
      - Report of the Sub Committee of Board of Governors of Residence Halls circa 1943 (Box 15)
      - Report of the Sub-Committee on Experimental Living Units 1970 (Box 15)
      - Single Student Housing Rate Study Committee Report 1974-1975 (Box 15)
      - Student Employment Survey 1979, 1979 (Box 15)
      - Task Force to Research Food Service Consolidation circa 1978 (Box 15)
      - University of Michigan Men's Residence Halls: Bulletin of Information 1952-53 circa 1953 (Box 15)
      - University of Michigan Residence Halls 1940 (Box 15)
    - Residence Halls
      - Analysis of Students 1973-1984 (by unit) (Box 15)
      - Counseling Program 1978 (Box 15)
      - Educational Philosophy 1978 (Box 15)
      - Energy Conservation 1979 (Box 15)
      - Historical and Building Data 1965 (Box 15)
      - Intramural Program 1939-1941 (organization and administration of) (Box 15)
    - Residence Halls (cont.)
      - Libraries 1972/73 (Box 15)
      - Loss Summary 1971-1975 (Box 15)
      - Night Security Program 1973 (Box 15)
      - Occupancy Reports 1968-1979 (Box 16)
      - Planning Committee 1971-1972 (Box 16)
      - Residence Hall House Staff Officials Reports 1940/41 (Box 16)
      - Room Types and Rates 1972-1981 (Box 16)
      - Scholarship 1939-1942 (Box 16)
      - Security Procedures 1971, 1973 (Box 16)
      - Study Spaces in 1978-1983 (Box 16)
    - Residential College 1962-1966 (Box 16)
    - Security, Housing 1977-1991 (includes statistics) (Box 16)
    - Single Student Housing 1966 (program statement) (Box 16)
    - Small Group Housing Committee 1969/74, 2 folders (Box 16)
    - Sororities 1968-1972 (Box 16)
    - South Quadrangle 1968 (Box 16)
    - Staff Review 1981 (of Housing) (Box 16)
    - Status of Women in Housing, Advisory Committee on 1973 (Box 16)
    - Student Advisory Committee on Housing 1965-1970 (Box 16)
    - Student Government 1968-1971 (residence halls) (Box 16)
    - Student Judiciaries and Discipline 1968 (Box 16)
    - Student Records Policy 1972-1978 (Box 16)
    - Student Vehicle Regulations 1966, 1968 (Box 16)
    - Surveys of Housing Division 1981, 1987 (Box 16)
    - Telephone Service 1970-1987 (Box 16)
    - Temporary Housing 1969 (Box 16)
    - Termination Information 1966-1971 (Box 16)
    - University Club 1971-1976 (Box 16)
    - University Housing Committee 1966-1970 (Box 16)
    - University Housing Council 1972-1979 (Box 16)
    - University Apartment Facilities 1966-1968 (Box 16)
    - University Regulations 1967 (Box 16)
    - University Terrace 1967-1973 (Box 16)
    - Visitation Policy
      - 1966/67 (Box 17)
      - 1968-1970 (Box 17)
      - 1973/74 (Box 17)
      - 1974/75 (Box 17)
    - Visitation Policy Survey 1971 (Box 17)
    - Visitors of the Opposite Sex 1966-1971 (Box 17)
    - Welcome Letter to Students 1971, 1978 (Box 17)
    - Women's Hours 1966-1969 (Box 17)
  - 1942-1994
    The Central Topical Files, 1942-1994 subseries (1.5 linear feet) (formerly called the Director of Housing files) appears to be a continuation of the Central Topical Files series. Of particular interest is the "Michigan House Plan" file, as it contains not only a copy of the plan, but background of and reaction to, the plan. The files came from the office of Robert C. Hughes, Director of Housing from 1966-1977.
    - Additional Student Housing
      - 1975-1977 (Box 23)
      - 1986 (Box 23)
    - Affirmative Action 1982-1986 (Box 23)
    - Alcohol, Task Force on 1977-1986 (Box 23)
    - Baits House 1984 (Box 23)
    - Business Administration, School of 1985-1986 (re: Executive Residence) (Box 23)
    - Conference and Catering Service 1989-1991 (Box 23)
    - Family Housing 1988-1989 (Box 23)
    - Family Housing Community Services Status Report 1982-83 1983 (Box 23)
    - Family Housing Day Care Center, proposal 1988 (cost analysis of) (Box 23)
    - Fraternities 1987 (undergraduate social) (Box 23)
    - Greek Task Force 1986 (Box 23)
    - Historical Building Data 1989 (Box 23)
    - Housing Goals 1977-1992 (Box 23)
    - Housing Statistics 1989-1994 (Box 23)
    - Lawyers Club 1979, 1988 (re: financing) (Box 23)
    - Michigan House Plan 1942-1971 (Box 23)
    - Minority Occupancy 1973-1993 (Box 24)
    - Race, Gender, and International Student Occupancy (Box 24)
    - Monthly Reports (to the Vice President for Student Affairs)
      - 1991, 3 folders (Box 24)
      - 1992 (Box 24)
    - Move-in Information 1988-1993 (Box 24)
    - Occupancy Report
      - Family Housing 1984-1988 (Box 24)
      - Residence Halls 1984-1990 (Box 24)
    - Off Campus Housing 1988-1994 (Box 24)
    - Organizational Charts 1987-1993 (Box 24)
    - Oxford Conference Center 1985-1987 (Box 24)
    - Procedure Manual 1976, 2 folders (Box 24)
    - Rate Committee Report
      - Family Housing 1979-1988 (Box 24)
      - Single Student 1977-1988 (Box 24)
    - Rates 1988-1994 (Box 24)
    - Reapplication 1988-1993 (Box 24)
    - Reports
      - Minority Recruitment and Retention, 1981, 1982 (Box 24)
    - Residence Hall Fact Sheets 1992 (Box 24)
    - Statistics 1984-1990 (re: housing) (Box 24)
    - Summer Conference Report 1983-1987 (Box 24)
    - Survey of Freshman Admits 1992 (SOFA) (Box 24)
    - Trotter House 1987 (re: finances) (Box 24)
    - University Residence Hall Council
      - 1980-1981 (Box 24)
      - 1981-1984 (Box 24)
      - 1984-1987 (Box 24)
      - 1987-1989 (Box 24)
  - 1958-1995
    The Central Topical Files series is largely composed of the files of housing directors John Feldkamp and Robert Hughes. The files are arranged alphabetically and document the Housing Divisions broad challenges in administering the residence halls, family housing, and Greek housing; challenges include: security, safety, and food quality. Of interest are the records of South Quad Residence Hall which contain a photo album, newspaper clippings and profiles of resident hall advisors. The problems that housing officials have had in enforcing their drug and alcohol policy in residence halls are well documented in six folders contained in this series.
    - Academic Advising in Residence Halls 1973-1992 (Box 41)
    - Academic Calendar 1970-1992 (Box 41)
    - Academic Space 1978-1982 (Box 41)
    - Affirmative Action 1978-1993 (Box 41)
    - Ann Arbor Tenants Union 1969-1972, 1991-1993 (Box 41)
    - Asbestos Abatement Program 1986-1988 (Box 41)
    - Association of College and University Housing 1988-1993 (Box 41)
    - Bicycle Policy 1966-1982 (Box 41)
    - Big Ten Chief Housing Officers 1978-1994 (Box 41)
    - Big Ten Chief Housing Officers-Statistical Surveys 1989-1994 (Box 41)
    - Brown Memorial Award, The Meyer M., Donald J., and Jenet K. 1958-1983 (Box 41)
    - Cable Television 1980-1993 (Box 41)
    - Cedar Bend I Houses 1964 (Box 41)
    - City-University Coordinating Committee 1985-1992 (Box 41)
    - College Housing Loan Program 1978-1982 (Box 41)
    - Collegiate Sorosis 1978-1985 (Box 41)
    - Commercial Solicitation in Residence Halls 1980-1981 (Box 41)
    - Community Living Guides and Drafts 1995 (Box 41)
    - Conference Action Council 1992-1993 (Box 41)
    - Conferences 1980-1992 (Box 41)
    - Consider, 1988-1993 (Box 41)
    - Cultural Society of Armenians from Istanbul 1986 (Box 41)
    - Damage and Vandalism in Residence Halls 1963-1981 (Box 41)
    - Delta Sigma Dance Incident 1992 (Box 41)
    - Dining Services 1980-1993 (Box 41)
    - Discipline Policy 1966-1983 (Box 41)
    - Discrimination 1973-1992 (Box 41)
    - Donation of University Property 1991 (Box 41)
    - Douglas McGreaham and Edward Siwik Endowment Fund 1981-1985 (Box 41)
    - Douglas McGreaham and Edward Siwik Murder 1980-1982 (Box 41)
    - Drug and Alcohol Policy
      - 1967-1972 (Box 41)
      - 1973-1976 (Box 41)
      - 1977-1993 (Box 41)
    - Drug and Alcohol Policy-Clippings 1970-1993 (Box 41)
    - Drug and Alcohol Policy-Regulations 1971-1993 (Box 41)
    - Drug and Alcohol Policy Reports 1975-1984 (Box 41)
    - Early Arrival Program 1992-1993 (Box 42)
    - End-of-Program Report on Housing Division Participation in Admissions Office Recruitment Programs 1992-1993 (Box 42)
    - Entrée Plus 1991-1994 (Box 42)
    - Eric Arnson 1978 (Box 42)
    - Eviction Policy 1976-1982 (Box 42)
    - Executive Chef 1980 (Box 42)
    - Executive Residence (President's House) 1988-1990 (Box 42)
    - Executive Residence (President's House) Inventory 1980 (Box 42)
    - Exterior Elements Design Review Committee
      - 1986-1994 (Box 42)
      - Memoranda 1981-1992 (Box 42)
      - Minutes 1980-1985 (Box 42)
    - Facilities Review Team 1992 (Box 42)
    - Fair Labor Standard Act-Residence Advisors 1967-1975 (Box 42)
    - Family Housing
      - 1992-1995 (Box 42)
      - Children's School 1973-1981 (Box 42)
      - Marriage Policy 1973-1975 (Box 42)
    - Financial Aid Survey 1992 (Box 42)
    - Firearms 1971-1975 (Box 42)
    - Fire Safety 1972-1986 (Box 42)
    - Food Borne Illness 1976-1990 (Box 42)
    - Food Service Inspection Summary 1989-1993 (Box 42)
    - Food Service for Athletes 1978-1982 (Box 42)
    - Foreign Student Housing 1983 (Box 42)
    - Forum for International Education 1980 (Box 42)
    - Fraternities
      - 1980-1991 (Box 42)
      - Correspondence
        - 1986-1990 (Box 42)
        - 1991 (Box 42)
        - 1992-1995 (Box 42)
      - Greek Activities Review Panel Manual 1995 (Box 42)
      - Policies and Statements 1990-1991 (Box 42)
      - Reports 1986-1992 (Box 42)
    - Freedom of Information Act 1977-1994 (Box 42)
    - Global College 1992 (Box 42)
    - Greek Task Force 1986-1989 (Box 42)
    - Good Stuff Distribution Plan 1992 (Box 42)
    - Grievance Procedure 1977-1980 (Box 42)
    - Helping Hands for the Homeless 1992 (Box 42)
    - Historical Housing and Building Data 1989 (Box 42)
    - Honors Housing 1963-1989 (Box 42)
    - Housing Internship Program 1977-1993 (Box 42)
    - Housing Rate Comparison 1980-1990 (Box 42)
    - Hubbard Field 1972-1980 (Box 42)
    - Human Powered Helicopter Project-Office Space 1991 (Box 42)
    - Inclement Weather Policy 1977-1991 (Box 42)
    - Information Systems Committee 1974-1988 (Box 42)
    - Inglis House, Inventory 1980 (Box 42)
    - Institute of Continuing Legal Education 1977 (Box 42)
    - Inter-Cooperative Council 1986-1993 (Box 42)
    - Interfraternity and PanHellenic Council Minutes 1990-1993 (Box 42)
    - Interior Design Services 1980-1991 (Box 42)
    - Judiciary Policy (Box 43)
      - Memoranda 1966-1993 (Box 43)
      - Reports 1962-1968 (Box 43)
    - Kalmbach Center-MBA housing 1983-1985 (Box 43)
    - Kelsey-Lynch Award 1980-1992 (Box 43)
    - Kemnitz Prints 1984-1990 (Box 43)
    - Keys 1968-1986 (Box 43)
    - Labor Say Weekend Move-in 1981-1993 (Box 43)
    - Libraries in Residence Halls 1973-1993 (Box 43)
    - Lighting and Landscaping Design 1975-1991 (Box 43)
    - Living-Learning Committee Report 1973 (Box 43)
    - Lynda Lee Haggis Kramer 1967 (Box 43)
    - Mailboxes 1966-1972 (Box 43)
    - Major Events Office 1991-1992 (Box 43)
    - Mandatory Health Insurance Plan for International Students 1981-1993 (Box 43)
    - Markley Incident 1991 (Box 43)
    - Meeting the Needs of Foreign Students in Housing, Report, 1991 (Box 43)
    - Mentorship Program circa 1990 (Box 43)
    - Michigan League 1992 (Box 43)
    - Michigan Union
      - Memoranda 1968-1981 (Box 43)
      - Miscellaneous 1978-1992 (Box 43)
      - Reports 1978-1989 (Box 43)
    - Military Service Call-Up (effect on leases) 1990-1991 (Box 43)
    - Minority Peer Advisors 1990-1991 (Box 43)
    - Minority Student Recruitment and Retention a Report by the Housing Division, 1980-1983 (Box 43)
    - Monroe Street Housing Development 1991 (Box 43)
    - Naming Residence Halls 1941-1950 (Box 43)
    - National Association of College Auxiliary Services (NACAS) 1978-1991 (Box 43)
    - North Campus Commons
      - 1990 (Box 43)
      - Memoranda
        - 1963-1990 (Box 43)
        - 1991 (Box 43)
      - Minutes 1963-1991 (Box 43)
    - North Campus Housing Service Building 1964-1981 (Box 43)
    - North Campus Low-Level Waste Facility 1987-1991 (Box 43)
    - North Campus Planning Committee 1967-1993 (Box 43)
    - Nu Sigma Nu 1981-1993 (Box 43)
    - Occupational Safety and Environmental Health 1973-1991 (Box 43)
    - Off-Campus Housing 1991 (Box 43)
    - Omega Psi Phi 1992 (Box 43)
    - Organizational Issues 1990-1991 (Box 43)
    - Oxford Housing/Conferences 1992-1993 (Box 43)
    - Painting Policy in Residence Halls 1971-1987 (Box 43)
    - PanHellenic-Correspondence 1990-1994 (Box 43)
    - Parent Orientation 1992-1993 (Box 44)
    - Parent Orientation Script (for video production) 1979-1990 (Box 44)
    - Parking 1974-1992 (Box 44)
    - Party Policy 1991-1993 (Box 44)
    - Personnel 1979-1993 (Box 44)
    - Peter Ostafin Scholarship 1982-1987 (Box 44)
    - Planning Options 1980 (Box 44)
    - Press Releases 1992 (Box 44)
    - Problems in Residence Halls 1988-1994 (Box 44)
    - Public Safety, Department of 1991-1992 (Box 44)
    - Purchasing 1991 (Box 44)
    - Quality Design Team Retreat "Qualtech," 1991 (Box 44)
    - Recycling 1988-1991 (Box 44)
    - Rental Properties 1975-1991 (Box 44)
    - Residence Halls Computing Center Proposal 1986-1992 (Box 44)
    - Research 1972-1991 (Box 44)
    - Research Proposal Summary 1992-1993 (Box 44)
    - Resed 1992-1993 (Box 44)
    - Residence Education 1983-1992 (Box 44)
    - Residence Hall Association (RHA) 1990-1993 (Box 44)
    - Residence Halls
      - Audit Reports 1977-1984 (Box 44)
      - Miscellaneous 1983-1993 (Box 44)
      - Rates 1976-1990 (Box 44)
    - Resident Safety 1990-1992 (Box 44)
    - Resident Satisfaction Survey Report 1992 (Box 44)
    - Resident Staff 1972-1993 (Box 44)
    - Senior Management Team
      - Memoranda 1987-1994 (Box 44)
      - Retreat Planning 1992-1993 (Box 44)
    - Service Award Dinner 1991-1992 (Box 44)
    - Sexual Harassment on the Job 1980-1991 (Box 44)
    - Sexual Orientation 1993 (Box 44)
    - Sigma Phi Epsilon 1992 (Box 44)
    - Smoking Policy 1986-1992 (Box 44)
    - Snack Bars in Residence Halls 1992-1993 (Box 44)
    - Solicitation 1971-1989 (Box 44)
    - Sororities 1973-1991 (Box 44)
    - South Quadrangle
      - Administrative Staff 1977-1993 (Box 44)
      - Articles circa 1992 (Box 44)
      - "Incident" 1990-1991 (Box 44)
      - Resident Advisor Biographies circa 1984
        - Anselmi-Axen (Box 44)
        - Bartone-Carruthers (Box 44)
        - Chamberlain-Christie (Box 44)
        - Dabbs-Falcon (Box 44)
        - Faye-Hausner (Box 44)
        - Haviland-Keenan (Box 44)
        - Kotsakis-Lynch (Box 44)
        - Makinin-Newman (Box 44)
        - Olson-Shapiro (Box 44)